mileageplanshopping.com 2015-03-15

# Privacy Policy - Shop Online at Mileage Plan Shopping

Alaska Airlines Mileage Plan™ Shopping Program has the highest respect for our Members' privacy and personal information. Except as provided in this Privacy Policy, the Mileage Plan™ Shopping Program (the "Program") will never release Member's personal information without express permission except for purposes of data verification and supplementation or such uses as are described in the Terms and Conditions.

Cartera Commerce, Inc., a Delaware corporation ("Cartera Commerce"), is the provider of the Program, which is sponsored by Alaska Airlines, Inc. and/or its affiliates (collectively, the "Program Sponsor"). This Privacy Policy describes Cartera Commerce's handling of your personal information it may collect through your participation in the Program.

Capitalized terms used herein and not otherwise defined have the meanings given to them in the Program Terms and Conditions.

INFORMATION COLLECTED AND HOW WE USE IT

In order to participate in the Program, you are required to provide certain information, including without limitation your NAME, MILEAGE PLAN™ NUMBER, and EMAIL ADDRESS.

We automatically log your IP address when you visit the Program website located at [www.mileageplanshopping.com](http://www.mileageplanshopping.com/) (the "Site"). The information logged allows us to track a user throughout their visit to the Site. We do not use this information to capture demographic or other information; rather, it is used simply in the administration of the Site.

The nature of the Program requires us to obtain information about your purchases at Participating Merchants. As a result, Participating Merchants send us transaction information (date and time of transaction, temporary ID number which only the Program can link to your account, sale amount and returned goods information) on a frequent basis. Cartera Commerce and/or the Program Sponsor use this information to properly add the Miles you've earned to your Program Account and Mileage Plan™ Account, respectively.

Information that identifies you personally will not be provided to, sold or disclosed to any third party without your express permission. Within Cartera Commerce and/or the Program Sponsor, we restrict access to your data to those employees, such as customer service representatives, who need such access to better serve you. In addition, Cartera Commerce and/or the Program Sponsor provide limited access to third party vendors who provide financial, administrative or other services in support of the Program. These vendors are restricted from using this data in any way other than to provide services to the Program and may not use or resell the data.

You will not be able to log on to the Site without enabling your browser to accept cookies. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from our Web server. The Site uses cookies when you log on to your Program Account, or at www.alaskaair.com, with your User Name and Password. These cookies allow us to remember you as you visit pages in the Site, so that you do not need to reenter your information. Our usage of cookies also allows us to track where users go when they visit the Site. We may use this "click-stream data" to deliver targeted offers to Mileage Plan™ Shopping Members and other similar functionality. Once you terminate your session, only your User Name will remain in the cookie on your hard drive.

The Site contains a number of links to Participating Merchants' web sites. We have not undertaken a review of the privacy policies or terms and conditions at such Participating Merchants' web sites, and we make no representations about the privacy policies or levels of security at these sites or the applicable terms and conditions. We are not responsible for the applicable terms and conditions or the privacy practices used by such Participating Merchants.

We will be sending you e-mails on a regular basis to advise you when your Program Account statement has been updated. Other e-mails may be sent from the Program informing you of updates or changes to the Program, Site, etc.

The Site takes commercially reasonable precautions consistent with general industry practices to protect Mileage Plan™ Shopping Members' information. When Mileage Plan™ Shopping Members submit sensitive information via the Site, we use our commercially reasonable efforts to ensure that their information is protected both online and off-line.

Information provided during our join or edit profile pages is encrypted and is protected with what is generally recognized as the best available encryption software in the industry - SSL. You will see the lock icon at the bottom of your browser and if you right click on the page, and view the page properties, you will see the site certificate. To learn more about SSL, follow this link: [http://www.verisign.com](http://www.verisign.com/).

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also use our commercially reasonable efforts consistent with general industry practices to protect user-information off-line. Mileage Plan™ Shopping Members' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only individuals who have a need to know such information to perform a specific job (for example, customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Furthermore, all such individuals are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. When an employee is hired, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our users' information is protected. Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are in a secure environment, off site. If you have any questions about the security at the Site, users can send an e-mail to [usersupport@cartera.com](mailto:usersupport@cartera.com) or otherwise contact us at the information below.

Mileage Plan™ Shopping Members may occasionally receive a newsletter or additional emails which provide information on additional products, services, special deals or other information which you may find to be of interest. Out of respect for the privacy of our users, we present the option to not receive some or all of these types of communications on the enrollment form. If you want to discontinue receiving these additional promotional communications, you may go to the "My Account" tab on the Site and uncheck the relevant opt-in box at any time. 

We also will send you Program and service announcement updates. Users are not able to unsubscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the Program and associated services. We communicate with Mileage Plan™ Shopping Members to provide requested services and address issues relating to their account, via email or phone, with information provided by the Mileage Plan™ Shopping Member. It is your responsibility to keep such information current.

You can update your Program information by going to the "My Account" tab on the Site and clicking on the Edit Account Options Link. Your changes will take effect immediately. If there is incorrect information in your Statement, please Contact Us and our customer service team will be glad to assist you. Please note that changes to your Program Account information will not update your Mileage Plan™ Account information. For complete details about the Mileage Plan™ Program, including Alaska Airlines' privacy policy, and to update your Mileage Plan™ Account information, visit [www.alaskaair.com](http://www.alaskaair.com/).

If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on the Site so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information or other information disclosed by you in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email prior to effecting such change. Mileage Plan™ Shopping Members will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. Otherwise, we will use information in accordance with the Privacy Policy under which the information was collected.

Though we make commercially reasonable efforts to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law or we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on the Program site.

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:

Email:| [USERSUPPORT@CARTERA.COM](mailto:USERSUPPORT@CARTERA.COM)  
---|---  
Address:| Mileage Plan™ Shopping Program  
Cartera Commerce, Inc.  
One Cranberry Hill, Suite 203  
Lexington, MA 02421  
Attn: Customer Care
